{
    "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-bahasa-inggris-tentang-expressing-threateningthrea-780",
            "question": "Contoh dialog bahasa inggris tentang expressing threatening/threat ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A : Hey, when do you want to pay your debt?<br>B : I will do my best to pay it next week.<br>A : It&#039;s better for you to keep your words, otherwise Don Corleone will kill you\u00a0<br>B : DOn&#039;t worry sir, I will keep my words",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-326",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Me : Mom, you are so beautiful in this night.\nMom : really? You never told me before mommy use beauty fash.\nMe : yes mom, you are A princess for daddy tonight, let tell Daddy, if Daddy shock, ask A opinion about you mom.\nMom : Ok , thankyou my sweetheart, i love you.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "lanjutan-jawaban-dari-in-the-developed-world-where-more-than-70-898",
            "question": "Lanjutan jawaban dari \"in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens already live in cities, urbanization is spread evenly, and population growth\" pilihan nya    a. has slowed\r\nb. would slow\r\nc. slowed\r\nd. had slowed\r\ne. will slow\r\n(simple future tense)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "d. in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens al already live in cities. urbanization is spread evenly. and population growth <u>had slowed</u>. <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "bisa saja isinya yang\u00a0<br>b. would slow, karena future pasti akan menggunakan will dan would adalah bentuk kedua dari modals tsb",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terdiri-dari-apa-sajakah-causative-have-itu-798",
            "question": "Terdiri dari apa sajakah causative have itu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Causative verb menunjukkan bahwa seseorang/sesuatu secara tidak langsung bertanggung jawab terhadap sebuah tindakan. Subjek tidak melakukan tindakan itu sendiri, tetapi justru menyebabkan seseorang/sesuatu yang lain melakukannya. Contoh:<br>- Yesterday I had my hair cut.<br>Pembicara pada kalimat diatas tidak memotong sendiri rambutnya, tetapi justru membuat orang lain melakukannya \u2013 Saya \u201cmenyebabkan\u201d mereka memotong rambut saya.<br>Have<br>Have merupakan causative verb yang umum. Ketimbang melakukan sesuatu dengan diri kita sendiri, kita \u201cmenyuruh\u201d orang yang lain untuk melakukannya. Bentuknya sebagai berikut:<br>Kata kerja \u201cto have\u201d + objek + past participle (verb 3). Contoh:<br>- I had my jacket cleaned yesterday.<br>- Did you have your computer fixed?<br>Terkadang kita menggunakan have sebagai causative verb ketika kita ingin melakukan tindakan oleh diri kita sendiri. Contoh:<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll do it by tomorrow morning. &gt;&gt;<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll have it done by tomorrow morning.<br>Dengan menggunakan causative, kalimat ke-dua diatas mengalihkan perhatian dari pelaku tindakan, dan lebih memberikan perhatian kepada tindakan yang sedang dilakukan. Ini kedengaran sopan dan profesional.<br>Get<br>Get sering digunakan ketimbang have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI got my computer fixed \u2013 I had my computer fixed. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>\u2022\tI got my jacket cleaned. \u2013 I had my jacket cleaned. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>Causative verbs sering digunakan bersama dengan pengalaman-pengalaman negatif. Pada situasi-situasi ini lebih umum menggunakan have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI had my wallet stolen. (Saya sebenarnya tidak menyebabkan dompet saya dicuri \u2013 seseorang mencuri dompet saya dariku)<br><span>\u2022\tShe had her window smashed.<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aku-belum-mengerti-dengan-jelas-tentang-past-perfect-tense-523",
            "question": "Aku belum mengerti dengan jelas tentang past perfect tense.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The PAST PERFECT TENSE indicates that an action was completed (finished or \"perfected\") at some point in the past before something else happened. This tense is formed with the past tense form of \"to have\" (HAD) plus the past participle of the verb (which can be either regular or irregular in form):\n    I had walked two miles by lunchtime. \n    I had run three other marathons before entering the Boston Marathon .",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>ita menggunakan Past Perfect (simple) tense untuk menunjukkan suatu tindakan di masa lalu berkaitan dengan tindakan lain sebelumnya di masa lalu. Bisa juga\u00a0pengertian Past perfect tensedigunakan utuk menjelaskan kalau sesuatu terjadi saat sebelum waktu spesifik.</span>Penggunaan Past Perfect Tense1. menceritakan sebuah tindakan yang sudah selesai sebelum tindakan lain di masa laluRumus = had + past participleContoh:<span>a.You had studied math before you moved to los angeles.<br>Kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>b. You had not studied math before you moved to Los angeles.<br>Kamu belum belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>c. Had you studied math before you moved to los angeles?<br>Apakah kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum ke los angeles?<br>2. kalimat pengandaian (Conditional Sentence) Type III</span><span>If + subject + Past perfect + would have + verb III<br>If we had known the answer, we would have told you<br>Seandainya kami telah tahu jawabannya, kami akan telah mengatakan padamu (kenyataanya kami sudah tidak tahu jawabannya)</span><span>3. kalimat tak langsung (reported speech)<br>Reported speech adalah kalimat yang digunakan untuk menjelaskan perkataan seseorang. Kalimat ini mengubah dialog menjadi kalimat biasa<br>Ann: I have searched all the rooms.<br>George: Ann said she had searched all the rooms.<br>George : Ann mengatakan bahwa dia sudah mencari semua kamar</span>untuk pembahasan selengkapnya tentang reported speech dalam berbagai tenses disini3 Rumus Past Perfect Tense<span>\u2022 Positif (+)<br>Subject + had + verb III + (past participle) + object<br>\u2022 Negatif (-)<br>Subject + had + not + verb III + object<br>\u2022 Tanya (?)<br>Had + subject + verb III + object ?</span>Contoh kalimat \u2013 Past Perfect tense:<span>They had been here before 1945 (+)<br>- mereka telah berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>They had not been here before 1945 (-)<br>- mereka belum berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>Had they been here before 1945 ? (?)<br>- apakah mereka telah berada disini sebelum 1945 ?</span><span>She had gone to Amsterdam when I called her (+)<br>- dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>She had not gone to Amsterdam when I called her (-)<br>- dia belum pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>Had she gone to Amsterdam when you called her ?<br>- apakah dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika kamu meneleponnya ?</span><span>Keterangan waktu (Adverb of time) yang umum digunakan dalam\u00a0past Perfect tense:<br>after, before, already, as soon as, just, yet, until, till, by the time that.</span><span>Past Perfect tense\u00a0juga digunakan untuk ungkapan seperti : \u201cI wish\u201d, \u201cas if/though\u201d and \u201cif only\u201d.</span><span>\u2022 I wish I hadn\u2019t gone there ( aku berharap aku tidak pernah pergi kesana )<br>\u2022 Jono looked as if he had done something terrible. ( Jono tampak seolah-olah ia telah melakukan sesuatu yang mengerikan )</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-contoh-berita-acara-serah-terima-pekerjaan-proyek-558",
            "question": "Ada yang tau contoh Berita Acara Serah Terima Pekerjaan (Proyek) dalam bahasa Inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><em>Handover Works (Project</em><span><em>)</em></span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ubahlah-menjadi-indirect-speech-1-kiki-said-whats-will-you-962",
            "question": "Ubahlah menjadi indirect speech!    1. Kiki said '' What's will you buy in the mall?''\r\n2. Mrs. Maria said '' Can you speak englsh well?''\r\n3. Yuda said Tika '' Are you from Surabaya?''",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau kalimatnya pertanyaan sebaiknya jangan pakai &#039;said&#039; tapi pakai &#039;asked (verb 2 dari ask)&#039;, jadinya...<br>1. Kiki asked me what would I buy in the mall : menggunakan me karena menceritakan kembali<br>2. Mrs. Maria asked me if I could speak English very well\u00a0: menggunakan me karena menceritakan kembali<br>3. Yuda asked Tika if\u00a0was she from Surabaya\u00a0: menggunakan she karena menceritakan kembali<br><br>semoga membantu :)",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. kiki asked me what would i buy in the mall.<br>2. Mrs. Maria asked me can i speak English well<br>3. Yuda asked Tika was she from Surabaya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buat-expressing-annoyance-2-orang-yang-berada-dalam-kelas-110",
            "question": "Tolong buat expressing annoyance 2 orang yang berada dalam kelas, jumlah percakapan 1 orang 5 percakapan    please help me :)\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i&#039;m so tired.<br>B: me too. it&#039;s boring here<br>C: and the whether feels so timid. i don&#039;t like it<br>D: me neither.<br>E: hey hey why don&#039;t we play soccer instead?<br>A: no thank you. i think it will cost much effort either<br><br>maaf gabisa buat yang bagus, isi umpatan gitu katanya",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}